Guide to the John Hope Franklin papers, 1891-2010, bulk 1950-2010 RL.10029
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advisory Board for the President's Initiative on Race (AB), 1972-2008; 14 boxes
  - Writings for Board Consideration
    - Booklets, 1991-1998, 2 folders (Box AB10)
      Arranged chronologically. Topics include race unity, minorities and U.S. foreign policy, racism, human rights, and the work of community organizations.
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box AB10)
      Includes short information sheets, poetry, and descriptions of community organizations. Mostly from the 1990s and undated.
  - Writings about the Advisory Board, 1997-2008
    Includes press clippings, magazine, and journal articles about the activities of the Advisory Board, memoranda on board member activities, proposals, information from the board's website and promotional materials, the executive order and charter for the board, and the ABPIR's final report, "One America in the 21st Century: Forging a New Future." Select oversize materials are in Box AB14.
    - Clippings, 1997, 3 folders (Box AB10)
    - Oversize clippings, 1997 (Box AB14)
    - Clippings from Al Moss, 1997 (Box AB10)
    - Clippings on race/racism, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box AB11)
    - Clippings, Miscellaneous Race Topics, 1997-1998 and undated (Box AB11)
      Includes some articles focused on the work of the Advisory Board. Oversize clippings removed to oversize box in series.
    - Executive order and charter for the creation of the Advisory Board (Box AB11)
    - Draft Advisory Board Goals and Actions, 1997 (Box AB11)
    - Work Plan Proposal, White House Working Group on Communications and Media/Press, 1997 (Box AB11)
    - Advisory Board membership information and contact information for board staff and associates, 1997 June 12 (Box AB11)
    - Clinton-Gore administration accomplishments, 1997 June 12 (Box AB11)
    - Personnel Information for Franklin and Ethics Rules for Special Government Employees, 1997 June 18 (Box AB11)
    - "A Challenge to the Nation," an address by Franklin before the North Carolina General Assembly, 1997 July 22 (Box AB11)
    - Work Plan and Process Modeling Thoughts, 1997 August 6 (Box AB11)
      Meeting with Franklin and Nissan Race Relations Task Team.
    - Draft Data Collection Plan and Work Plan, 1997 August 21 (Box AB11)
    - Excerpt from a talk given before the meeting of the National Leadership Summit on Race Relations, 1997 September 27 (Box AB11)
    - Working Group Proposals Presented by President's Initiative on Race Staff, 1997 October 6 (Box AB11)
    - Recommendations for the President's Initiative on Race from Erskine Bowles, 1997 October 8 (Box AB11)
    - One America Website Printout, 1997 November 6, 2 folders (Box AB11)
    - Tentative List of Subjects for Monthly Meetings, 1997 November 10 (Box AB11)
    - One America Website Printout, 1997 November 14 (Box AB11)
    - One America: Conversations that Bring Us Together, information packet, 1997 November 24 (Box AB11)
      Information about and guidelines for hosting conversations throughout the country designed to gather input on the President's Initiative on Race. Documents include "How to Hold a One America Conversation in 10 Steps," and "How to Conduct a Constructive Dialogue: A Guide for One America Conversation Hosts."
    - Work Plan Proposal: White House Working Group on Communications and Media/Press, 1997 (Box AB11)
    - Press releases and statements from the board, 1997 (Box AB11)
      Includes statements about the board made by Clinton Administration Press Secretary Mike McCurry and pamphlets for the President's Initiative on Race.
    - Draft Advisory Board Goals and Actions, 1997 (Box AB11)
    - Executive Order and Charter for the Creation of the Advisory Board, 1997 (Box AB11)
    - Weekly Reports, 1997 (Box AB11)
      Reports on activities of ABPIR members and staff, August-November, 1997, including conferences, town hall meetings, board subcommittee meetings, and updates on personnel.
    - Information about "Promising Practices," 1997 and undated (Box AB11)
      Information about a President's Initiative on Race program.
    - "The Mission of the Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race," proposed op-ed for The New York Times, 1997 (Box AB11)
    - Clippings, 1998, 3 folders (Box AB11)
    - Oversize clippings, 1998 (Box AB14)
    - Clippings from Al Moss, 1998 (Box AB11)
    - Oversize clippings on race/racism, 1997-1998 (Box AB14)
    - Oversize clippings about miscellaneous race topics, 1997-1998 and undated (Box AB14)
    - Clippings on John Hope Franklin, 1993-1998 (Box AB14)
    - Press report on Advisory Board meeting in Phoenix, Arizona, 1998 January 16 (Box AB11)
    - Education Opportunity Zones, Strengthening Our Urban and Rural Schools, 1998 January 26 (Box AB11)
    - Press report on Advisory Board meeting in San Jose, 1998 February 16 (Box AB11)
    - John Cole Cartoon of ABPIR, 1998 September 20 (Box AB11)
      Includes Franklin letter of response to Cole cartoon from the Durham Herald Sun.
    - "Talking, Not Shouting, About Race," Franklin editorial in the New York Times, 1998 June 13 (Box AB11)
    - "Things I have learned as Chair of the President's Advisory Board," John Hope Franklin, St. Petersburg Rotary Club, 1998 February 20 (Box AB11)
    - "Straight Talk," by Jeffrey Zaslow, USA Weekend, 1998 March 20-22 (Box AB11)
    - Email responses to "Straight Talk," by Jeffrey Zaslow, USA Weekend, 1998 March 20-22 (Box AB11)
    - Letters of response to "Straight Talk," by Jeffrey Zaslow, USA Weekend, 1998 March 20-22, 3 folders (Box AB12)
    - Statewide Days of Dialogue: Talking Points For Events Around the Country, 1998 (Box AB12)
    - "One America in the 21st Century: The President's Initiative on Race," March 1998 (Box AB12)
      Guide for conducting a discussion on race.
    - Talking Points for American Indians, April 13, 1998 (Box AB12)
    - The Culminating Event, 1998 September 18 (Box AB12)
      Memos, press, releases, and talking points pertaining to the presentation of the ABPIR's report and findings to President Clinton.
    - Presentation of Final Report to President Clinton, Press Clippings, 1998 September 21 (Box AB12)
    - "One America in the 21st Century: Forging a New Future," The Advisory Board's Report to the President, September 1998, 2 folders (Box AB12)
      Final report on the Advisory Board's experiences and observations, including specific recommendations on how the President might proceed with regard to race relations in the U.S.
    - Changing America: Indicators of Social and Economic Well-Being by Race and Hispanic Origin, 1998 September (Box AB12)
      Report compiled by the Council on Economic Advisers for the President's Initiative on Race.
    - Telephone Lists, 1998 (Box AB12)
      Telephone directories for ABPIR members and staff.
    - Weekly reports, 1998 January-May (Box AB12)
      Reports on activities of ABPIR members and staff, including conferences, town hall meetings, board subcommittee meetings, and updates on personnel.
    - Weekly reports, 1998 June-September (Box AB12)
    - Activity Report Forms, 1998 and undated (Box AB12)
    - One Year Progress Report, Background Material, 1998 June 9 (Box AB12)
    - President Clinton's FY 1999 Balanced Budget: "Education: Preparing Our Children for the 21st Century" (Box AB12)
    - "Understanding President Clinton's Initiative on Race," Larry D. Terry, 1999 (Box AB12)
    - Clippings, 1999 and undated (Box AB12)
    - President Clinton's Report to the Nation, draft, 1999 (Box AB12)
      Missing several pages.
    - Pathways to One America in the 21st Century: Promising Practices for Racial Reconciliation, 1999 January, 2 folders (Box AB12)
      Report on community and government agencies, nonprofit organizations, and businesses that seek to promote racial reconciliation and community building.
    - "A Half-Century of Presidential Race Initiatives: Some Reflections," John Hope Franklin, Journal of Supreme Court History, 1999, vol. 24, no. 2 (Box AB12)
    - Advisory Board responses to media coverage, 1997-2000 (Box AB12)
    - "A Half-Century of Presidential Race Initiatives," Smithsonian National Museum of American History, 2001 April 18 (Box AB12)
    - "One America in the 21st Century," Chris Rogers, 2008, 2 folders (Box AB12)
      Book manuscript about the President's Initiative on Race from Yale University Press.
    - Some activities of the Advisory Board and the President's Initiative on Race, undated (Box AB12)
    - Questions and Answers about One America in the 21st Century: The President's Initiative on Race," undated (Box AB12)
    - "The Work of the Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race," undated drafts (Box AB12)
    - Speeches and outlines, including "A Vision for One America," undated (Box AB12)
    - Untitled notes (Box AB12)
    - List of resumes in file of the Committee on Nominations, undated (Box AB12)
    - Undated memos about Advisory Board activities, community groups, and community outreach (Box AB12)
  - Artifacts, 1993-1997 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by title. Includes several items, including toys, a banner, and a bookmark donated to the ABPIR.
    - Air Force One flyer (Box AB13)
    - Black American Heritage Flag (Box AB13)
      Removed to oversize materials Box AB15.
    - Character Lines clothing company, information and brochures, 1998 24 February (Box AB13)
    - Eracism Packet, 1993-1995 (Box AB13)
    - Medical Research bumper sticker (Box AB13)
    - "Our Legacy" Jigsaw Puzzle, 1997 and undated (Box AB13)
    - Recovering Racist Pin and Information Sheet (Box AB13)
    - Spirituality bookmark (Box AB13)
    - Underground Railroad Multimedia Activity Set, 1993/1996 (Box AB13)
    - Black American Heritage Flag and Pin (Box AB14)
      Includes clippings, photographs, and correspondence pertaining to flag designer Melvin Charles, 1985-1998.
    - Arkansas Democrat Gazette, Little Rock, 1957, The Central High Crisis (Box AB14)
      Historic Front Pages from the Arkansas Democrat and Arkansas Gazette, Aug. 29-Oct. 4, 1957
- Audiovisual Recordings (AV), 1959-2009; 27 boxes; 1 film can
  Access Restrictions
  Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Some use copies are available. Please contact the Rubenstein Library for more information before requesting or coming to use these materials.
  Scope and Contents
  These videos, film, and sound recordings created by or assembled by John Hope Franklin are a rich source of information about his life and career and about U.S. race relations and 20th century society.
  Materials are arranged into three subseries: ABPIR (Advisory Board for the President's Initiative on Race), Recordings of Franklin, and Recordings of Others. Formats include videocassettes, audiocassettes, audio reels, microcassettes, and moving image film.
  Recordings are arranged in chronological order.
  - Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race (ABPIR), 1996-1998 and undated; 1
    The ABPIR (Advisory Board for the President's Initiative on Race) subseries is made up primarily of recordings of advisory board meetings and short commercially produced videos relating to race, for example, public service announcements.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original media recordings are closed to use. Some viewing or listening copies may be available. Please contact the Rubenstein Library staff before requesting or coming to use these materials.
    - The Hating Pot, 1996 August 13; 1
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0157)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0003)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0028)
    - Skin Deep, 1997 August 27; 2
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0165)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0010)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0035)
    - Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race meeting, 1997 December 17; 3
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0107)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0108)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0109)
    - Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race meeting, 1997 July 14; 4
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0101)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0102)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0103)
    - Racism: Unraveling the Fear, 1997 November 7; 5
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0096)
    - Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race meeting, 1997 September 30; 6
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0104)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0105)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0106)
    - Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race meeting, 1998 February 11; 7
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0110)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0111)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0112)
    - Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race meeting, 1998 January 14; 8
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0115)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0116)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0117)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0118)
    - Race in America: A Message from Los Angeles, 1998 January 17; 9
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0100)
    - Health Care Rx: Access for All, 1998 July 10; 10
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0097)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0098)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0099)
    - Advisory Board to the President's Initiative on Race meeting, 1998 June 18; 11
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0113)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0114)
    - A Half Century of Presidential Race Initiatives: Some Reflections. Economic Club of Detroit, 1998 October 26
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL.10029-CS-0060)
    - America, You're My Hometown, circa 1990-1998; 12
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0011)
    - An American Message, circa 1990-1998; 13
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0155)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0001)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0026)
    - Feast of Peace, circa 1990-1998; 14
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0156)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0002)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0027)
    - Introducing Zahmu, circa 1990-1998; 15
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0158)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0159)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0004)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0029)
    - My So Called Community, circa 1990-1998; 16
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0160)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0005)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0030)
    - National Arts and Humanities Month PSA, circa 1990-1998; 17
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0161)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0006)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0031)
    - New York by Leonard Bernstein, circa 1990-1998; 18
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0162)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0007)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0032)
    - Real Heroes: Providing Positive Role Models for Today's Young Minorities, circa 1990-1998; 19
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0163)
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0164)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0008)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0009)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0033)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0034)
    - Sing this Life Together, circa 1990-1998; 20
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0012)
      - Preservation master audiocassette (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0015)
      - Use copy audiocassette (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0013)
      - Use copy audiocassette (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0014)
    - Sports Agency, Sports Management, Sports Marketing, and Race Relations in America, circa 1990-1998; 21
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0166)
      - Preservation master betacam-sp videocassette (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL10029-Bcam-0011)
      - Use copy DVD videodisc (Box AV15, Video-disc RL10029-DVD-0036)
    - 31st Race Relations Institute, undated; 22
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0094)
    - Civil rights grievance of L.B. Jones of Taylor, MS, undated; 23
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0001)
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0002)
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0003)
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0004)
      - Original microcassette audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-MCS-0001)
      - Original microcassette audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-MCS-0002)
      - Original microcassette audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-MCS-0003)
    - Outside the Lines: Race & Sports Running in Place, undated; 24
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0095)
    - The Heart Knows Better, undated; 25
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL10029-VHS-0119)
    - University Forum, "The President's Initiative on Race," JHF with Dr. Jean Moore, Temple University, Public Radio, circa 1998
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV28, Audio-cassette Rl.10029-CS-0059)
  - Recordings of John Hope Franklin, 1960-2009 and undated; 2
    The Recordings of Franklin subseries documents a wide range of Franklin's activities from interviews, to appearances in historic or racially themed documentaries and educational videos, to lectures and speeches on race, race relations in the U.S., and the historian's role in interpreting history. One set of tapes record a lengthy oral history interview of Franklin by A. Ballard, National Humanities Center, in which Franklin recounts events in his life from his earliest years in Oklahoma to his decision to go to the University of Chicago. Another audiocassette includes an interview of T.S. Currier with Franklin.
    - Address to Jounalists Club, 1960 April 8; 26
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0001)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0102)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0126)
    - Self Hate, 1963 November 9; 27
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0003)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0104)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0128)
    - This Rebellious Generation, 1963 September 19; 28
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0002)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0103)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0127)
    - Civil Rights Revolution in Historical Perspective, American Negro History Week, 1965 February 11; 29
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0004)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0105)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0106)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0129)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0130)
    - The History of Americans of African Descent, 1967 February 20; 30
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0005)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0107)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0108)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0131)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0132)
    - Interview with JHF, Chairman of History Department, University of Chicago, 1968 October 23; 31
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0006)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0109)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0133)
    - Presidential Address of JHF to the Southern Historical Association, 1971 November 18; 32
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0017)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV16, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0031)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV18, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0078)
    - Interview, T. S. Currier with JHF, 1972 January 2; 33
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0016)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV16, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0018)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV18, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0065)
    - The Historian and Public Policy, 1974; 34
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0019)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV16, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0009)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV18, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0056)
    - The Historian and Public Policy, Edward and Nora Ryerson Lecture, 1974; 35
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0020)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV16, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0016)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV18, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0063)
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0007)
      - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL10029-RR-0008)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0110)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV20, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0111)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0134)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV21, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0135)
    - JHF guest appearance on People to People, 1974 December 29; 36
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10029-CS-0018)
      - Preservation master compact disc (Box AV16, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0022)
      - Use copy compact disc (Box AV18, Audio-cd RL10029-CD-0069)